

Nikolay Pasyuk

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Contacts 🔠 🚳 in 🗖 🥊











nickivanov18.12@gmail.com



+375 (33) 684-02-08



MINSK, BELARUS

About me

Hello, I am a person who has a strongpassion for programming.

I have experience in creating SPAwith React/Redux/TypeScript.

I would like to find project workand full-time employment in a company witha modern approach acollaborative development and team.

Expert Skills

React/Redux/Redux Toolkit JavaScript/TypeScript Unit tests/StoryBook AXIOS/REST API MaterialUI GIT/GITHUB HTML5/CSS3/SCSS

Languages

English Pre-Intermediate in progress

Work Experience

MY PROJECTS AT FRONT-END DEVELOPER (PART-TIME, FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT)

Playing cards:

Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Axios, Team developement, refactoring, bug fixing, deploying. Link to Github

Social network:

Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, ReduxThunk, Redux-form, Reselect; Refactoring, bug fixing. Organizing correct apparchitecture. Link to Github

Todolist:

Stack: JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, StoryBook, Material UI; Using TypeScript for best code control; deploying; Covering code with unit tests. Link to Github

MASTER ELECTRICIAN

BudProgress-2008, OOO | 2017 - 2021

maintenance of power equipment, personnel management

Education History

IT-INCUBATOR

 Frontend developer (React/Redux/TypeScript/JS), 2021-2022

FOREIGN LANGUAGE SCHOOL **STREAMLINE**

• English courses, 2020-2021

BELARUSIAN NATIONAL TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY

Energy Engineer, Electric power systems and networks, 2014-2020